(train horn blowing)
(whistling
The Farmer in the Dell)
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(gun cocking)
(Mouzone)
THAT'S FAR ENOUGH.
DROP YOUR LAUNDRY
AND TURN SLOWLY.
SO YOU GONNA
ROB ME NOW?
I NEED TO
REMIND YOU WHO I AM?
OMAR. ISN'T IT?
PULL IT SLOWLY.
THEN TOSS IT.
OH. I WILL MOVE SLOW.
I AIN'T TOSSIN'
NOTHIN'. BOW TIE.
SO WHATEVER YOU GONNA DO.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL GO AHEAD
AND MAKE IT QUICK.
I KNEW YOU'D COME BACK.
I TRUST YOU DIDN'T
LOSE SLEEP OVER IT.
WORRYIN' ABOUT YOU
WOULD BE LIKE
WONDERING IF
THE SUN GONNA COME UP.
I AIN'T ABOUT TO
WILD OUT OVER IT.
WHAT I WANT TO KNOW
IS HOW YOU FOUND ME.
YOUR BOY. HE DIDN'T
GIVE YOU UP EASY.
AIN'T NO SUGAR-WATER
RUN THROUGH 'EM VEINS.
YOU KILL HIM?
HE'S RESTING.
I SEE YOU FAVOR A .45.
TONIGHT I DO.
AND I KEEPS ONE
IN THE CHAMBER.
IN CASE YOU PONDERIN'.
(police sirens wailing)
NICE SHOWPIECE YOU GOT THERE.
WALTHER P.P.K. .380.
DOUBLE ACTION.
HEAR THEM WALTHERS
LIKE TO JUMP SOME.
AS WILL YOU.
WITH ONE IN YOUR ELBOW.
THAT GUN AIN'T
GOT ENOUGH FIREPOWER
TO MAKE MY JOINT USELESS.
IT DEFINITELY WON'T
STOP ME FROM EMPTYIN'
OUT HALF MY MAG.
YOU MIGHT NOT HIT ME.
THIS RANGE?
AND THIS CALIBER?
EVEN IF I MISS.
I CAN'T MISS.
I ADMIRE A MAN
WITH CONFIDENCE.
I DON'T SEE
NO SWEAT ON YOUR BROW
NEITHER. BRO.
(rain pattering)
(train horn blaring)
I SUPPOSE WE COULD
STAND HERE ALL NIGHT.
SUPPOSE WE COULD.
OR SETTLE THIS
ONCE AND FOREVER.
(clicking)
I WANT TO ASK YOU
SOMETHING. BROTHER.
OMAR LISTENIN'.
(officers chattering
over police radio)
(officer #1)
I'm going to the West.
(officer #2)
All right.
Peace out.
HERE WE GO.
(man)
Yo. I need some
face time with the man.
Hold on.
I'll holler back
at you. man.
THAT'D BE SHAMROCK.
ASSUMING
STRINGER BELL IS THE MAN.
NOW WE WAIT
FOR THE RETURN CALL.
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
LESTER.
CAN YOU ACTUALLY BELIEVE
WE FUCKIN' SOLD
THE WIRETAPS TO THE TARGETS.
FOR A WEEK AT LEAST.
MAYBE WE DUCKED A BULLET.
MAYBE WE CLEAN
THIS MESS QUIETLY.
THROW SOME HORSESHIT AT
WHATEVER REPORTER SHOWS UP.
AND THE MAYOR
FORGIVES AND FORGETS.
WE'RE READY TO
MOVE ON THIS.
RIGHT?
AS SOON AS WE GET THE WORD.
WE SHUT DOWN ALL 3 ZONES.
TOSS EVERYONE INTO WAGONS.
THERE'LL BE
NOTHING LEFT OF IT
BEFORE MIDNIGHT SHIFT.
SO WHAT THE FUCK
ARE WE WAITIN' ON
FOR A DAY AND HALF?
WHY ISN'T THE HALL
CALLIN' US?
(beeping)
(phone ringing)
(woman)
Mayor's office.
COMMISSIONER BURRELL
FOR MAYOR ROYCE.
I'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
HOLD ON. COLEMAN.
COME ON.
LET THE MAN TALK. HUH?
EXCUSE ME. MAYOR. I HAVE
COMMISSIONER BURRELL
ON THE LINE.
HE SAYS IT'S URGENT.
I'LL BET IT IS.
HE WANTS TO MOVE. CLARENCE.
HE WANTS TO
CLEAN THIS SHIT UP
YESTERDAY. AND SO DO WE.
TELL HIM TO HOLD.
GO AHEAD. GENE.
LOOK. I'M NOT A POLITICIAN.
I'M AN ACADEMIC.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT FROM
A PUBLIC HEALTH PERSPECTIVE
THERE ARE REMARKABLE THINGS
HAPPENING IN THE FREE ZONES.
NEEDLE EXCHANGES.
ON-SITE BLOOD TESTING.
CONDOM DISTRIBUTION.
MOST OF ALL.
WE'RE INTERACTING
WITH AN AT-RISK COMMUNITY
THAT IS LARGELY ELUSIVE.
I MEAN. WE'RE... WE'RE EVEN
TALKING SOME OF THESE PEOPLE
INTO DRUG TREATMENT.
AND THAT'S JUST
WHAT U.M. AND BON SECOURS
HAVE BROUGHT TO THE TABLE.
IF THIS THING
WERE SANCTIONED.
MY DEPARTMENT COULD PUT
PUBLIC RESOURCES INTO PLAY.
YOU PEOPLE CAN'T
SEE THE FOREST HERE.
ODELL?
WHEN THE STORY BREAKS.
THE MINISTERS WILL
SURELY BE AGAINST YOU.
AND MOST OF THE CITY COUNCIL
WILL BE WALKING SIDEWAYS
AWAY FROM
YOUR ADMINISTRATION.
(Watkins)
AND MY GUESS IS THE GOVERNOR
AND THE LEGISLATURE
WILL USE THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO PISS ON THE CITY
FROM A GREAT HEIGHT.
AND WASHINGTON? OH...
CAN YOU IMAGINE HOW FAR
THE UNITED STATES
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
IS GONNA CRAWL UP
YOUR ASS BEHIND THIS?
CRIME IS DOWN. ODELL.
MEDICAL PEOPLE
ARE TELLING ME
THIS COULD WORK.
I MEAN. A 14% DECLINE
IN FELONIES CITYWIDE.
I MIGHT BE UNTOUCHABLE
ON THIS. NOW. LOOK.
WE NEED TO THINK.
SEE IF WE CAN
KEEP THIS THING GOIN'
WITHOUT CALLIN' IT
WHAT IT REALLY IS. HUH?
JESUS.
OH. NOW. THERE'S GOT TO
BE A WAY. I WANT YOU
TO TALK THIS THING OUT.
HEY. ERV.
THANKS FOR HOLDIN'.
YES. BUT...
(Mayor chattering
indistinctly on phone)
YES. I UNDERSTAND.
THEN I'LL WAIT
TO HEAR FROM YOU.
WE'RE TO HOLD OFF
ON ANY ACTION IN HAMSTERDAM.
NO ARRESTS.
NO MOVEMENT
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.
HE SAYS HE WANTS TO REGROUP.
DETERMINE THE MOST EFFECTIVE
COURSE OF ACTION.
TRANSLATE THAT
FOR ME. WILL YOU. ERV?
I DON'T SPEAK HIS
FUCKED-UP LINGO.
ROYCE IS FIGURIN' A WAY
TO PUT ALL OF US
IN THE GUILLOTINE
AND KEEP THE BLOOD
FROM SPRAYING
ANYWHERE NEAR THE HALL.
SHIT. I'LL BE GODDAMNED
IF I'M GONNA GO OUT
LIKE THAT.
BENT OVER IN PUBLIC.
I CAN SPIN THE STORY
JUST AS WELL AS
THAT MOTHERFUCKER.
YOU'RE GONNA GO
TO THE PRESS?
NOT ME.
BUT I KNOW
A SLICK LITTLE BASTARD
WHO WILL HAPPILY PUT
HIS HONOR'S SHIT
IN THE STREET.
SOMETHIN' FUNNY
ABOUT THAT?
'CAUSE I LOOK
IN THE PAPER
AND I SEE ALL
THESE FEDERAL GRANTS
COMIN' DOWN.
BUT NONE FOR B. AND B.
YOU'RE EXPECTING WHAT?
PAYOUT.
A BIG PAYOUT FOR
WHAT WE PUT IN. MAN.
FEDERAL DOLLARS ON THEM
HOWARD STREET REHABS.
YOU GAVE MONEY UP FRONT?
$250.000. YEP.
TO CLAY DAVIS.
HOW YOU KNOW?
WHAT YOU SAYIN'?
HE'S RUNNIN' GAME?
NO. HELL. NO.
HE AIN'T THAT BRAZEN.
MMM-MMM.
LET ME GUESS.
HE'S TOLD YOU
ABOUT THE FAUCET.
OR WAS IT THE GOOSE
THAT LAID THE GOLDEN EGG?
YOU EVER ACTUALLY
MEET THE MAN?
DID YOU EVER ACTUALLY
SEE ANY OF YOUR CASH
REACH ANYONE IN AUTHORITY?
YEAH. I MET THE GUY AT
THE FEDERAL BUILDING.
YEAH. I MET HIM.
YEAH? WHAT OFFICE?
HE CAME DOWN TO THE LOBBY.
HE RAIN-MADE YOU.
A GUY SAYS IF YOU PAY HIM.
HE CAN MAKE IT RAIN.
YOU PAY HIM.
IF AND WHEN IT RAINS.
HE TAKES THE CREDIT.
IF AND WHEN IT DOESN'T.
HE FINDS REASONS FOR
YOU TO PAY HIM MORE.
CLAY DAVIS RAIN-MADE YOU.
NO. MAN. HE... HE GOT
THEM BUILDIN' PERMITS
IN NO TIME AT ALL. MAN.
I MEAN. WE BRIBIN'
THESE MOTHERFUCKERS.
HE GOT THE CITY
CONTRACTOR'S MONEY BACK.
HOW MUCH?
$35.000 SO FAR.
ON THE $250.000
YOU GAVE HIM?
IT'S FOR BRIBIN'
THE MOTHERFUCKERS.
THERE ARE NO BRIBES!
YOU REALLY THINK
A STATE SENATOR
IS GOING TO RISK HIS...
HIS SALARY AND
HIS POSITION BY WALKING
INTO A FEDERAL OFFICE
WITH A BRIEFCASE
FULL OF DRUG MONEY?
I SEEN. UH. CHUNKY.
CHUNKY COATES.
CHUNKY COATES
GETS HIS GRANT MONEY
SAME WAY EVERYONE DOES.
HE FILLS OUT APPLICATIONS.
HE MAKES SURE
THE PLANS MEET SPEC.
THEN HE PRAYS LIKE HELL.
THIS IS AN OLD
GAME IN THIS TOWN.
AND CLAY DAVIS?
THAT GANEF WAS BORN
WITH HIS HAND
IN SOMEONE'S POCKET.
I JUST WISH
YOU'D RUN IT
BY ME SOONER.
NOW HERE'S SHAMROCK
RETURNIN' BODIE'S CALL.
(Bodie)
Talk light.
Yo. the man said
he'd see you
same time as always.
You know the spot.
DURING THE FIRST CALL.
SYDNOR HAD EYES ON SHAMROCK
OVER IN WEST BALTIMORE.
ALL RIGHT?
NOW LOOK AT THIS.
AT THE TIME.
STRINGER BELL WAS
AT THE PRINT SHOP.
SO IT COULDN'T BE
A FACE-TO-FACE MEET.
WE DIDN'T CATCH
A CALL BETWEEN
STRINGER AND SHAMROCK.
HOW CAN THAT BE?
STRINGER'S PHONE ISN'T
ON THE SAME NETWORK
AS EVERYONE BELOW HIM.
RIGHT YOU ARE. MA'AM.
BELL'S NOT USING
BERNARD'S BURNERS.
AND SHAMROCK HAS
A SEPARATE PHONE
FOR CALLIN' BELL.
WE CAN'T HEAR THOSE CALLS
BECAUSE THE SYSTEM'S
COMPARTMENTALIZED.
THEY'RE SOME
TRICKY MOTHERFUCKERS.
A WEEK OR SO UP
ON BERNARD'S PHONES
AND WE'LL HAVE EVERYBODY.
UP TO AND INCLUDING SHAMROCK.
TANGLED UP IN
CONSPIRACY COUNTS.
BUT BELL OR BARKSDALE?
NOT UNLESS WE CAN
PLUCK THEIR CELL NUMBERS
OUT OF THE AIR.
WHERE YOU
HEADED?
TOY STORE.
HE LEGALIZED DRUGS
IN SPECIAL ZONES?
IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
MAJOR COLVIN LOST
THE NECESSARY PERSPECTIVE
THAT IS REQUIRED FOR COMMAND.
NOW. WE WERE ALL
UNDER PRESSURE
TO REDUCE CRIME
BEFORE YEAR-END.
AND HE RESPONDED
POORLY TO THAT PRESSURE.
PRESSURE BY WHO? MAYOR?
I'M JUST EXPLAINING TO YOU
THAT THE PRESSURE
WAS APPLIED
ALL DOWN THE LINE.
FROM HEADQUARTERS
TO THE DISTRICT COMMANDERS
TO THE SHIFT
AND SECTOR SUPERVISORS.
SO COLVIN'S
14% DECLINE
WAS BULLSHIT.
(scoffing)
AND THEY'RE SELLIN' DRUGS
WITH POLICE PERMISSION
IN WESTERN?
THE DEPARTMENT
IS READY TO
SHUT THAT MESS DOWN
WITH MASS ARRESTS.
I'M ON TOP OF IT.
WHY DON'T YOU MOVE?
(laughing)
THE MAYOR SAYS WAIT.
WHY?
I THINK HE'S GONNA MAKE
SOME KIND OF SHOW.
SPIN IT SO THAT
I TAKE THE WEIGHT
FOR SOMETHIN'
THAT HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.
AND EVERYTHING TO DO
WITH THE PRESSURE
THAT MY COMMANDERS
WERE GETTING FROM CITY HALL.
GOING PUBLIC AND
PUTTING THE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THIS BACK AT CITY HALL
IS THE ONLY MOVE
I HAVE LEFT. RIGHT?
I MEAN. I SPIN ROYCE
BEFORE HE SPINS ME.
AND YOU WANT ME TO. UH...
NO. NO. NOT YOU.
YOUR PAL. TONY GRAY.
IF HE'S GONNA
TAKE A RUN AT ROYCE.
HE'S GONNA NEED
AMMUNITION. RIGHT?
(sighing)
I DON'T HAVE
A RELATIONSHIP
WITH GRAY.
I DO HAVE ONE WITH YOU.
AND. COUNCILMAN. YOU OWE ME.
(Fitzhugh)
WHAT'S UP. HOTSHOT?
I GOT A TECHNICAL QUESTION.
REMEMBER THOSE ANALOG UNITS
WE USED TO USE
TO PULL CELL NUMBERS
OUT OF THE AIR?
C.F.-SOMETHIN'-SOMETHIN'.
YEAH. CELL FREQUENCY
IDENTIFICATION DEVICE.
THE TRIGGERFISH. YEAH.
THAT ONE.
IT COULD FLAG A NUMBER.
RIGHT. WITH THE OLD
ANALOG MACHINES.
WE USED TO HAVE TO
FOLLOW THE GUY AROUND.
STAY CLOSE WHILE
HE USED THE PHONE.
NEW DIGITALS?
BING.
YOU JUST PULL THE NUMBER
RIGHT OFF THE CELL TOWER.
SO. YOU GOT ANY
DOWN OUT AT WOODLAWN
THAT DADDY CAN BORROW?
WHAT ABOUT YOURS?
WHAT?
CITY HAS 3 OF 'EM.
IF I REMEMBER RIGHT.
HOMELAND SECURITY GRANT
SENT 'EM TO YOU.
EVERY BIG COUNTY
DEPARTMENT IN THE STATE.
NO FUCKIN' WAY.
(engine starting)
THANKS.
I DOUBTED YOU. TOMMY.
I TOLD YOU IT WAS BIG.
IF WE PLAY IT RIGHT.
HE WANTS ME TO
TURN THE INFORMATION
OVER TO TONY GRAY.
LET HIM USE IT. HE FIGURES
IF TONY'S GONNA BE
RUNNIN' AGAINST THE MAYOR.
HE'LL TAKE AIM AT ROYCE
AND NOT THE DEPARTMENT.
YOU MAY WANT TO
BRING TONY IN ON IT.
KEEP HIM VIABLE
AGAINST THE MAYOR.
BUT RIGHT NOW.
YOU NEED TO FIND OUT
WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
FIRSTHAND.
DO YOU KNOW
THIS MAJOR COLVIN?
TO SHAKE HANDS. MAYBE.
IF BURRELL'S
PAINTING HIM THE VILLAIN.
COLVIN MIGHT BE ANXIOUS
TO TELL SOMEONE HIS
SIDE OF THE STORY.
(rock music playing on radio)
McNULTY. MAJOR CRIMES.
SULLIVAN.
MINOR IRRITATIONS.
YOU GOT ANYTHING BACK THERE
THAT'S LIKE THE OLD C.F.I.D..
BUT DIGITAL?
FOR CATCHIN'
CELL NUMBERS?
CATCHIN' WHO?
YOU KNOW.
A TRIGGERFISH MACHINE.
TRIGGERFISH.
FOR CELL NUMBERS.
HOW ABOUT I LOOK
AROUND THERE ON MY OWN?
YES. THIS IS
COUNCILMAN CARCETTI
OVER AT THE HALL.
I'M TRYIN' TO
REACH MAJOR COLVIN.
(woman)
I'm sorry.
but he's on vacation.
I'M AWARE OF THAT
BUT I'M TRYIN' TO REACH HIM
ON MUNICIPAL BUSINESS.
Well. I can put you
through to his voicemail.
NO. NOT HIS VOICEMAIL.
I SAID I HAVE TO
REACH HIM IMMEDIATELY.
Immediately?
RIGHT.
How about his cell phone?
HIS CELL?
YEAH. THAT WOULD BE FINE.
All right.
(music playing on stereo)
(grunting)
(Cutty)
ALL RIGHT. THAT'S ENOUGH.
(swearing)
YEAH. I KNOW. IT HURTS.
BUT YOUR FISTS
GONNA BE LIKE
ROCKS AFTER AWHILE.
JUSTIN. COME HERE.
ALL RIGHT. I WANT YOU
TO PUSH ME IN MY CHEST.
YOU AIN'T GOT TO
DO IT HARD.
THAT'S HOW
YOU WERE STANDIN'.
YOU AIN'T HAD NO
WEIGHT ON YOUR BACK FOOT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
NO CENTER OF GRAVITY.
PLUS. IF YOU GET
YOUR STANCE RIGHT.
THEN YOU GOT THE MEANS
TO PUT YOUR HIP
INTO THE PUNCH.
(grunting)
RIGHT?
THAT'S WHERE YOUR
POWER'LL COME FROM.
YEAH. BUT WHAT HAPPEN
WHEN WE GET HIT?
SAY WHAT?
WE GET HIT.
EVEN WITH THIS PAD.
YOU GONNA GET TRUCKED.
ALL THIS STUFF FALLIN' APART.
YEAH. THE HEAVY BAG. TOO.
YEAH. WHERE YOU GET
THIS STUFF AT?
THE TOWN OF BEDROCK?
(boys laughing)
(man)
NO. HE SAY. "NOBODY."
SO YOU GONNA HAVE
TO WAIT RIGHT HERE.
(Stringer)
WHAT YOU MEAN.
"WAIT RIGHT HERE?"
YOU KNOW WHO I AM. BOY?
MAN SAY
HE WANT TO SEE AVON.
MAKIN' ME WAIT TO
SEE MY OWN PARTNER.
HE NEW. STRING.
FUCK THAT.
LOT OF NEW FACES
ROUND HERE. MAN.
WAY TOO MANY. YOU ASK ME.
GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
(hip-hop music
playing on stereo)
WHERE AVON AT?
HE'LL BE ALONG SHORTLY.
THAT'S GOOD.
'CAUSE I CAME TO
SEE YOU. ANYWAY.
WHAT YOU NEED?
I NEED YOU TO HIT SOMEBODY.
WHO WE HITTIN'?
CLAY DAVIS.
THE CLAY DAVIS?
DOWNTOWN CLAY DAVIS?
IS THAT SUPPOSE TO MEAN
SOMETHIN' TO ME. MAN?
THAT NIGGA NEED TO BE GOT.
SHIT. STRING.
MURDER AIN'T NO THING.
BUT THIS HERE IS SOME
ASSASSINATION SHIT...
I TELL YOU
YOU GETTIN' SOMEBODY.
YOU GETTIN' HIM.
I AIN'T ASKIN'.
DAMN. STRING. I DON'T KNOW...
NIGGA.
I GOT TO REMIND YOU
WHO THE FUCK YOU WORK FOR?
HEY. YO.
I THINK SLIM GONNA HAVE
TO SIT THIS ONE OUT. BOSS.
SO YOU FINNA
GO HIT A STATE
SENATOR NOW. HUH?
YO. YOU KILL
A DOWNTOWN NIGGA
LIKE THAT.
THE WHOLE WORLD
GONNA STAND UP
AND TAKE NOTICE.
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT
THE STATE POLICE.
FEDERALS. ALL OF THAT.
YOU NEED A
DAY OF THE JACKAL TYPE
MOTHERFUCKER. BASICALLY.
TO DO SOME SHIT LIKE THAT.
NOT A ROUGH-AND-TUMBLE
NIGGA LIKE SLIM.
THAT NIGGA TOOK
OUR MONEY. MAN.
I SEEN IT COMIN'.
WELL. HE GOT TO GO.
NO. YOU A FUCKIN'
BUSINESSMAN.
YOU WANNA
HANDLE IT LIKE THAT.
YOU DON'T WANNA
GET ALL GANGSTER WILD
WITH IT AND SHIT. RIGHT?
WHAT I TELL YOU
ABOUT PLAYIN' 'EM
FUCKIN' AWAY GAMES?
(Avon)
YEAH.
THEY SAW YOUR
GHETTO ASS COMIN'
FROM MILES AWAY. NIGGA.
YOU GOT A FUCKIN'
BEEF WITH THEM?
THAT SHIT IS ON YOU.
SO. WE AIM THIS AT
THE NEAREST CELL TOWER.
THE ONE THAT WOULD BE
THE CONDUIT FOR CALLS
COMIN' TO AND FROM
OUR BOY. BELL.
AND WE LET RIP.
(both exclaiming)
FUCKIN' HELL.
(Freamon)
LOOKS LIKE
BALTIMORE WHITE PAGES
WITHOUT ANY NAMES.
BUT THE PATTERN
TRACE'LL PULL THAT DOWN.
YOU KNOW. IF WE KNOW
THE APPROXIMATE
TIME OF BELL'S CALL.
WE COULD START
JUST BY PULLIN' CALLS
OFF THAT TOWER AT THAT TIME.
THAT COULD BE THOUSANDS.
YEAH. THAT'S THE BASE LINE.
BUT WE GET A SECOND HIT
AND THAT LIST
COMES DOWN TO DOZENS.
AND AFTER A 3RD OR 4TH...
THEN WE'VE GOT
HIS NUMBER.
YOU KNOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT THIS WAS JUST
SITTIN' OVER AT I.S.D..
GATHERIN' DUST.
WE'RE GOING TO BE ON
THESE MOTHERFUCKERS
FOR REAL NOW. LESTER.
WELL. THEY DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS TECHNOLOGY YET.
FOR ONCE THEY CAN'T
CHANGE AND ADJUST.
IT'S GENIUS.
(chattering)
(singing)
NEED SOMETHING?
YEAH. HOW MUCH
YOU MAKE. MAN?
WHAT?
ON THEM TEES?
HOW MUCH YOU MAKE?
FAIR PROFIT.
NO MORE THAN THAT.
YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
SELL SWEATS
WITH HOODIES.
SINCE THE SEASON'S
CHANGIN' AND ALL.
WHERE YOU LIVE AT?
(man)
YELLOW TOPS. YELLOW TOPS.
GOT 'EM YELLOW TOPS.
BODIE BROADUS.
THE MAN WITH THE HANDS.
I HEARD YOU WAS. UM.
OPENIN' UP A GYM
OR SOMETHIN'.
YEAH. TRYIN' TO.
I'M LOOKIN' TO
GET UP WITH AVON.
THOUGHT YOU WAS OUT.
HEY. MAN. THAT'S WHY
I CAME TO YOU.
I MEAN. I FEEL LIKE
THE WAY WE LEFT IT.
I CAN'T JUST ROLL UP
ON THE MAN. YOU KNOW?
(cell phone beeping)
HEY. YO. IT'S ME.
YO. I GOT THAT
HITTER HERE WITH ME.
YEAH. THE SOLDIER
THAT WALKED IN AND OUT.
YEAH. HE WANT TO
SEE THE TOP MAN.
(moaning)
YOU SLAM SHIT LIKE THAT.
YOU GONNA FALL OUT ONE DAY.
(people chattering)
I'M GOOD.
I'M TRYIN' TO
SCHOOL YOU. BOY.
AND YOU JUST
DON'T WANNA KNOW.
(sniffing)
I'M COOL.
I'M GOOD.
(Bubbles)
WHITEY SALE. WHITEY SALE.
YEAH. 1 FOR 3.
3 FOR 5.
WHITEY SALE.
WHITEY SALE. WHITEY SALE.
WHITEY SALE. HERE.
1 FOR 3. 3 FOR 5.
WHITEY SALE. WHITEY SALE.
WHITEY SALE. WHITEY SALE!
(Bodie)
All right. so what you
want me to tell the man?
Yo. I'll give word up.
then I'll hit you back.
SHAMROCK.
4:40 P.M.
(tapping desk)
(cell phone ringing)
B. AND B. ENTERPRISES.
(man)
We need to have lunch.
ALL RIGHT. HOLD ON.
I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
(phone beeping on)
(burping)
YO.
(man)
Hey. it's me.
WHAT'S GOOD?
(cell phone ringing)
(music playing)
YEAH. IT'S ME.
(Shamrock)
Yo. tell the hitter.
tell him the tall man
will pick him up.
(Bodie)
Right.
4:47.
7-MINUTE WINDOW.
THERE'S 892 PHONE NUMBERS.
THAT'S OUR BASE LINE.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY.
YEP.
STAY THE FUCK THERE. MAN.
YO.
JIMMY!
ON THE CLEAN PHONE.
HE JUST HIT YOUR
FRIEND'S NUMBER.
THE ONE OFF
THE BUSINESS CARD
YOU GAVE ME.
THE WESTERN?
HIS CELL.
SHOULD WE BE
WORRIED ABOUT THIS?
NO.
(Avon)
A BOXING GYM. HUH?
AIN'T A PROPER ONE YET.
THAT'S WHY I
ASKED TO SEE YOU.
(hip-hop music playing)
SO. WHAT YOU KNOW
ABOUT TAKIN' CARE OF
SOMETHIN' LIKE THAT?
NOT A DAMN THING.
BUT I KNOW THAT
SWEET SCIENCE.
AND I GOT SOME KIDS
WHO ARE INTERESTED.
BUT WHAT I GOT
A NEED FOR. BROTHER.
IS EQUIPMENT.
MAN. THESE KIDS
GONNA GET RAINED ON.
THEY NEED HEADGEAR.
THEY NEED GUARDS. CUPS.
YOU KNOW.
SO THEY CAN TAKE THE HIT.
SHOOT. YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYIN'. MAN.
I SEEN YOUR PICTURE
ON THEM GLOBE POSTERS
BACK IN THE DAY.
LITTLE UNDERCARD SHIT.
MAYBE. YOU KNOW.
YEAH. BUT STILL.
YOU WAS GOLDEN GLOVES.
FOR A MINUTE.
BUT I HAD
A PHYSICAL DEFECT.
WHAT. YOU GOT A GLASS JAW?
NO. FOREHEAD. NIGGA.
CRANIUM SHOT'LL
DO YOU WRONG. MAN.
YO. LOOK HERE. MAN.
YOU SEE
THE NEW HEAVY BAGS?
LOOK. FREESTANDIN'. MAN.
ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS ADD WATER.
HMM.
THEN YOU GOT...
SPEED BAGS.
RIGHT THERE. RIGHT?
YOU GOT THIS HEADGEAR
RIGHT HERE. IT'S NEW.
LOOK. PROTECT
THE CHEEK AND THE CHIN.
YOU KNOW?
AND I KNOW I CAN GO AROUND
AND COLLECT A DOLLAR
HERE AND A DOLLAR THERE.
BUT I'M TRYIN' TO
PUT TOGETHER A SELECT
GROUP OF PEOPLE. RIGHT?
I CALL 'EM MY...
MY GOLD CIRCLE CLUB.
AND THEY GONNA MAKE
A SUBSTANTIAL CONTRIBUTION
AND JUST GET THIS
THING ROLLING RIGHT.
I MEAN.
I'M GONNA PUT THEIR NAME
AND PICTURE UP ON
THE WALL IN THE GYM.
WHAT. YOU TRYIN' TO
GET ME TO JOIN A CLUB?
NO. MAN. I'M JUST SAYING.
THERE...
THERE'S ALL SORTS OF LEVELS.
THAT... WE GOT THE.
WE GOT THE SILVER CLUB.
WE GOT THE BRONZE CLUB.
MAN. FOR MOTHERFUCKERS
WHO REALLY DON'T
WANT TO DIG THAT DEEP.
COME ON. MAN. CHECK IT OUT.
NO. MAN.
I AIN'T GOT NO TIME FOR
THIS BULLSHIT. MAN.
AND YOU KNOW I DON'T
WANT MY FUCKIN' NAME
AND FACE ON NO DAMN WALL.
YOU CRAZY. NIGGA?
HOW MUCH MONEY
YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
$10.000.
(Avon)
SEE HIM GO THROUGH
ALL THAT FOR $10.000?
(both laughing)
MAN. SLIM.
GO GET HIM
$15.000 CASH. MAN.
YO...
SHIT.
ALL RIGHT. LATER. MAN.
HEY. YOU TAKE CARE
OF THEM LITTLE NIGGAS.
YOU HEAR?
MAN. NO DOUBT. BRO.
(phone ringing)
(sighing)
(Bodie)
Yeah.
YO. YOU TALK TO HIM?
Fat man wanna parlay.
ALL RIGHT. YOU GOOD.
HOOK ME UP.
Yeah. all right.
(beeping)
YOU CHECK OUT
WHAT I SENT YOU?
YEAH.
YOUR INFORMATION'S GOOD.
SO. WE CAN TALK
ON THE REAL SIDE
NOW. HUH?
(Stringer)
Tell your man
I'm good for tomorrow.
(Bodie)
Yo. I'll hit you back.
NOW WE'RE COOKIN'.
CUTTIN' BUTTER
WITH A HOT KNIFE.
NEXT TIME STRINGER BELL TAKES
A CALL OFF THE BASE LINE.
HE'S OURS. GAME OVER.
(Massey)
MMM-HMM.
(crickets chirping)
SO. IT AIN'T WHAT
IT MIGHT SEEM TO YOU.
THAT MAN THERE IS MY BROTHER.
(cell phone ringing)
BUT IF IT KEEP ON
LIKE IT BEEN. THEN...
OH. FUCK.
YOU GOT PROBLEMS?
I STIRRED UP SOME SHIT
WITH THIS HAMSTERDAM MESS.
THAT'S 'CAUSE
YOU WAS BEHIND THAT.
THAT MADE ME COME
TO YOU WITH THIS.
LOOK LIKE YOU AND ME
BOTH TRYIN' TO MAKE
SENSE OF THIS GAME.
SPEAK YOUR MIND. RUSSELL.
(soul music playing on stereo)
(vehicles passing)
WE TWO GOOD?
YEAH.
WE GOT Y'ALL OUT FRONT.
LET'S GO. P-SQUARE.
YOU LOOK HEALTHY.
FOR A MAN WHO WAS GUT-SHOT.
YOU REACHED OUT
TO A THIRD PARTY
WHO ENGAGED ME
IN THE PURPOSE OF
HOLDING YOUR TOWERS.
THAT THIRD PERSON'S WORD
WAS YOUR WORD.
AS HE REPRESENTED YOU.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND I RAN THOSE
EAST BALTIMORE
GENTLEMEN OFF.
I HELD UP MY END
OF THE AGREEMENT.
AT LEAST FOR AS LONG AS
I WAS PHYSICALLY ABLE.
YOU DID.
YOUR MAN THEN SET UP
A MEET AT BUTCHIE'S BAR.
YOUR MAN TOLD OMAR LITTLE
THAT I WAS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE TORTURE
OF A YOUNG BOY
WHO WAS CLOSE
TO MR. LITTLE'S HEART.
YOUR MAN. IN EFFECT.
SOUGHT TO HAVE ME HIT.
OMAR TOLD YOU THAT
AND YOU BELIEVE
THAT MOTHERFUCKER?
HE DOESN'T STRIKE ME
AS A MAN WHO
WOULD TELL STORIES.
EVEN AT THE POINT OF DYING.
SHIT.
(muttering)
PROPOSITION
JOE PACKAGE.
THE INNER WORKINGS
OF YOUR ORGANIZATION
DON'T CONCERN ME.
IF THERE'S A WAY.
I MEAN. IF MY MAN...
IF HE MADE A MISTAKE HERE.
THEN I'M WILLIN'
TO PAY THE COST.
HOW CAN WE FIX IT?
YOU WANT MONEY?
MONEY?
YEAH.
THIS IS BUSINESS.
BUSINESS IS
WHERE YOU ARE NOW.
BUT WHAT GOT YOU HERE
IS YOUR WORD
AND YOUR REPUTATION.
WITH THAT ALONE.
YOU'VE STILL GOT
AN OPEN LINE TO NEW YORK.
WITHOUT IT. YOU'RE DONE.
MY MAN'S STILL ON PAPER.
I CAN PUT HIM
IN A SPOT THAT GOT
HEAVY ARTILLERY.
I AIN'T TALKIN' ABOUT
PISTOLS. I'M TALKIN' ABOUT
MINI TEC-9s.
SHOTGUNS.
THEY EVEN GOT GRENADES
IN THAT MOTHERFUCKER.
WELL. THAT'S A
AUTOMATIC FALL.
SO. I'M HOPIN' YOU COULD
KEEP THAT SHIT TO 5.
LOOK. IF YOU HIT
THE JOINT.
HIS PEOPLE ARE GONNA TRY
AND TAKE THE RAP FOR IT.
THEY GONNA SAY ALL
THAT FIREPOWER IS THEIRS.
SO ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS JUST HIT HIM
WITH THE PAROLE BACKUP.
LOOK. I CAN'T MAKE
NO PROMISES.
IT'S GONNA BE
A NICKEL. AT LEAST.
COME ON. MAN.
HIM AND ME...
I'M GONNA DO MY BEST.
ALL RIGHT?
NOW. HE'S ALWAYS
AT THIS PLACE?
NO. HE COME AND GO.
BUT IT'S THE SPOT
SINCE THE WAR STARTED.
HE MUST HAVE DONE
SOMETHIN' TO YOU.
NO. IT'S JUST BUSINESS.
(computer beeping)
ALMOST FORGOT.
THIS CAME IN FOR
YOU LAST NIGHT.
SAID SHE CALLED
YOUR CELL PHONE.
BUT YOU DIDN'T ANSWER.
HAD A NICE VOICE.
LIKE A KITTY CAT.
(Massey chuckling)
(Freamon)
WE'RE ON.
(man)
He said for you
to be there. half-pint.
(Bodie)
Yeah. okay.
(typing)
STRINGER BELL. THAT'S HIM.
THERE IT IS.
YEAH. BUT FOR HOW LONG?
HE COULD TOSS THAT
BURNER AT ANY MOMENT.
I GOT RHONDA.
YOU RAISE DANIELS.
(Freamon)
OK.
RONNIE? YEAH.
WE'RE ON STRINGER'S PHONE.
LIEUTENANT.
YOU SHOULD GO STRAIGHT TO
THE JUDGE. I'LL MEET YOU
THERE WITH AN AFFIDAVIT.
LESTER'S RAISING DANIELS.
McNULTY'S CALLING PEARLMAN.
WATCH THAT FOOTWORK. BABY.
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE IT TO HIM. NOW.
YEAH. TAKE IT TO HIM. NOW.
I'M A BEAST. COACH.
ALL RIGHT. BOY.
DON'T BE GLOATIN' ON IT.
YO. WHEN WE GONNA
HAVE SOME REAL FIGHTS?
YOU KNOW. ONE OF
THEM TOURNAMENT THINGS.
YEAH. WE GLADIATORS. SON.
Y'ALL GOT MORE
FIRE THAN SKILLS.
YOU AIN'T READY FOR NO
FULL-BLOWN THING JUST YET.
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT'D BE GOOD FOR Y'ALL
TO SPAR WITH SOME
BOYS YOU DON'T KNOW.
A NIGGA STEP IN MY HOUSE.
HE GETTIN' DROPPED.
YO. I MET THESE
FELLAS AT THAT GYM
OVER ON PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE.
I'LL SEE IF THEY WANNA
ROLL THROUGH. ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT.
YOU DON'T RETURN
A COUNCILMAN'S CALLS?
I'M OFF THIS WEEK.
TAKING A LITTLE
ACCRUED VACATION.
YEAH. AND I HEARD WHY.
I'M HERE FOR YOUR
SIDE OF THIS STORY.
IF I CAN'T GET THAT
THEN WHATEVER COMES OUT
OF BURRELL'S MOUTH
IS GONNA STAND.
YOU GOOD WITH THAT?
WHAT DID YOU DO. MAJOR?
AND WHY THE FUCK
HAVEN'T THEY SHUT IT DOWN?
WE'VE SEEN THAT
LAW ENFORCEMENT'S
STEAMROLLER APPROACH
IS JUST SPITTING IN THE WIND!
I REALLY THINK.
I REALLY THINK THAT
YOU'RE ONTO SOMETHING
HERE. CLARENCE.
BUT IF YOU KEEP IT UP.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT
THEY'LL BE CALLING YOU
THE MOST DANGEROUS
MAN IN AMERICA.
WELL. I KNOW
IT MAY APPEAR THAT WE'RE
VULNERABLE HERE. HUH?
BUT IF WE ENFORCE
THE DRUG LAWS
EVERYWHERE ELSE
IN THE CITY
AGGRESSIVELY. HOW...
HOW CAN THEY SAY
WE'RE NOT A LAW AND
ORDER ADMINISTRATION?
NOW THERE'S GOT TO BE
A MIDDLE GROUND HERE
THAT WE HAVE YET TO FIND.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME WAY
TO ACCOMPLISH THIS
WITHOUT TURNIN'
EVERYTHING UPSIDE DOWN.
THIS USED TO BE ONE
OF MY WORST CORNERS.
(Carcetti)
THIS IS THE NEIGHBORHOOD
WHERE A COP GOT SHOT
LAST SUMMER. RIGHT?
DOZERMAN.
LOOKS QUIET NOW.
SO DO MOST
ALL MY CORNERS.
G-MAN.
(phone ringing)
(knocking)
SO. WHAT'S UP?
SHUT THE DOOR.
IN 10 MINUTES WE'RE GONNA
HAVE AN AFFIDAVIT
FOR A CITY JUDGE TO SIGN.
IT'S FOR RUSSELL BELL'S
DIRTY CELL.
IT'S A GOOD PULL.
IT IS IF BAY WIRELESS
DOESN'T TAKE 5 DAYS
TO PROCESS IT.
YOU OWE ME. FITZ.
THAT WHOLE PORT CASE
CAME DOWN EARLY
BEHIND SOME UGLY SHIT
IN YOUR HOUSE.
NOW.
I DON'T CARE HOW YOU DO IT.
BUT I NEED MY WIRE TODAY.
(chattering)
THESE GUYS WERE
IN RADIO CARS
2 MONTHS AGO.
CHASING CALLS.
CLEARING CORNERS.
I PULLED 'EM
TO DO FELONY FOLLOW-UP.
MORE POLICE WORK.
LESS BULLSHIT.
AND THAT'S WHY
MY CRIME IS DOWN.
THE NUMBERS ARE TRUE.
(phones ringing)
WHAT DID HE DO?
CHURCH BURGLARIES.
14 OF 'EM.
LET'S GO.
AH. MADEMOISELLE.
IS IT AFFIANT
OR AFFIANT?
I'VE NEVER BEEN...
I'VE NEVER BEEN
CLEAR ON THAT.
(piano music playing)
YOU BEEN HUNTIN'
THIS GUY BELL
FOR A LONG TIME.
HAVEN'T YOU. JIMMY?
A WHILE. YEAH.
(Judge Phelan)
NAME'S FAMILIAR TO ME.
THAT THING THAT WE DID
A FEW YEARS BACK.
WAS. WAS HE THE. UH...
YEAH.
WHAT'S DONE
IS DONE. JIMMY.
NOW. FOR YOUR
OWN FUCKIN' SAKE.
JUST LET IT GO.
COME ON.
AS THE AFFIANT.
DO YOU SOLEMNLY
SWEAR AND ATTEST
THAT THE INFORMATION
CONTAINED IN THIS DOCUMENT...
THAT'S THE MOST
SIGNIFICANT DROP IN CRIME
IN THIS DISTRICT
IN RECENT HISTORY.
(clapping)
(woman)
WE STILL GOT
SOME HARD-LOOKIN' BOYS
OUT ON THEM STREETS.
AND. SERGEANT. YOU KNOW THEM
LITTLE MINI-MOTORCYCLES?
THEY KEEPIN' ME
UP AT NIGHT.
WE'RE WORKIN' ON THAT.
LOOK. I HAVE BEEN LIVING
IN THIS PART OF
THE CITY MY WHOLE LIFE.
AND I CAN TELL YOU
SOMETHING. WE WEREN'T ANY
ANGELS WHEN WE WERE KIDS.
AND THOSE. UH. HARD BOYS
YOU TALKIN' ABOUT.
HALF OF 'EM. THEY'S JUST
PLAYIN' GANGSTER.
THEY AIN'T NO DIFFERENT
FROM WHAT WE WERE.
SHIRTS AND DRAWERS
A LITTLE LONGER. IS ALL.
(all laughing)
THE ONE THING
I DO. UH. MISS ABOUT.
UH. MY NEIGHBORHOOD.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE NEIGHBORHOOD
I CAME UP IN.
SEE.
WE KNEW THE POLICE.
(all murmuring agreement)
SEE?
WE HAD A WHITE
POLICE OFFICER.
OUR HOUSE WAS ON HIS BEAT.
ON HIS FOOT BEAT.
AND HE WOULD BE
SITTIN' OUT
TALKIN' TO MY MOTHER
DAMN NEAR EVERY NIGHT.
I MEAN. JUST SITTIN' OUT
ON HER STOOP. JUST TALKIN'.
AND I'M TELLIN' YOU THAT
THIS MAN. HIS NAME WAS.
UH. FRASIER O'LEARY.
YOU KNOW. HE EVEN KNEW
MY GRANDMOTHER BY NAME.
YOU KNOW?
Y-Y-YES. MA'AM.
LET'S MOVE ON TO
THE TIP-LINE INFORMATION...
I'M SO SORRY. BABY.
I'M REAL SORRY.
BUT I WAS NOT FINISHED.
(all agreeing)
YOU SEE. LET ME
TELL YOU SOMETHIN'.
I HAVE NOT SEEN THAT
FACE-TO-FACE POLICIN'
IN A LONG WHILE.
IN A VERY LONG WHILE.
UNTIL LAST WEEK.
A YOUNG OFFICER.
BLACK OFFICER.
CAME BY MY STOOP.
I WAS SITTIN' OUT.
GAVE ME HIS CARD.
HIS NAME IS REGGIE BALLARD.
(sergeant agreeing)
IS HIS NAME. RIGHT?
AND HE SAT.
AND HE TALKED TO ME.
WE JUST TALKED.
AND. SEE. NOW I KNOW
HIS NAME AND FACE
AND HE KNOWS
MY NAME AND FACE.
YOU SEE?
AND I'M GONNA
TELL YOU SOMETHIN'.
THAT IS HOW IT SHOULD BE.
(all clapping)
MY SON WANNA OPEN UP
ONE OF 'EM SNOWBALL
STANDS ON THE STREET.
DO WE NEED
A PERMIT FOR THIS?
YOU EVER SEEN A WEST SIDE
COMMUNITY MEETIN'
LIKE THIS ONE?
(sergeant)
IN FACT. THE FOLKS DOWNTOWN
AT MINOR PRIVILEGES TELL ME
THAT STANDS AREN'T
ALLOWED IN THE CITY
RIGHT-OF-WAY AT ALL.
NOW THEY DO SAY
IT IS POSSIBLE TO HAVE
A SNOWBALL STAND
BEHIND THE SIDEWALK.
WHY ARE YOU REALLY
DOWN HERE. COUNCILMAN?
I MEAN. THIS AIN'T
EVEN YOUR DISTRICT.
I'M INTERESTED.
AND I HAVE THE PUBLIC
SAFETY SUBCOMMITTEE.
YOU SEE THAT BUILDIN' THERE?
IT WAS THE
OLD STRYKER BUILDIN'.
IT WAS A FUNERAL PARLOR.
THE LAST STOP
BEFORE THE CEMETERY
FOR WEST SIDE WHITE FOLK.
BACK WHEN THERE WERE
STILL SOME OF THOSE AROUND.
RIGHT ABOUT
THE TIME THAT. UH.
JIM CROW WAS BREAKIN' UP.
BACK IN THE EARLY '60s.
SOMEBODY ASKED
OLD MAN STRYKER.
THEY SAY. "STRYKER.
"YOU GONNA CHANGE YOUR POLICY
A-A-AND START
BURYIN' BLACK FOLK?"
AND STRYKER SAID.
"YEAH. ON ONE CONDITION.
THAT I CAN DO 'EM
ALL AT ONCE."
THAT'S SICK.
BUT YOU KNOW SOMETHIN'?
I HAD A LOT OF RESPECT
FOR THAT MAN.
'CAUSE. UNLIKE MOST FOLKS.
I ALWAYS KNEW WHERE HE STOOD.
I'M DOIN' MY JOB.
(chuckling)
LOOK. I DONE
SHOWED YOU THE GOOD.
COME ON.
LET ME SHOW YOU THE UGLY.
(phone ringing)
HEY.
HOW COME SO QUICK?
STRINGER BELL'S GIVEN NAME.
RUSSELL.
FOR NOW?
AHMED.
WE'RE ON THE TOP
OF THE MOUNTAIN.
(beeping)
(man)
RED TOPS OVER HERE.
COME GET 'EM. COME GET 'EM.
RED TOPS.
(people chattering)
(Carcetti)
THIS IS IT?
(Bunny)
1 OF 3.
HOW DID YOU
MAKE THIS HAPPEN?
I JUST DID IT.
I GOT TIRED OF HEARIN'
FOLKS TALK ABOUT
WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE
OR WHAT THEY WOULD DO
IF IT WAS UP TO THEM.
(man)
BOTTLE ROCKETS.
GOT THEM BOTTLE ROCKETS.
SO. WHAT. THIS IS
ABOUT YOU MAKIN' A MARK?
NO. I AIN'T ANALYZED IT
ALL THAT DEEP.
I AIN'T CLAIMIN'
NO KIND OF VICTORY.
NEITHER.
I WILL SAY I...
I'M GLAD I TRIED.
GO ON. COUNCILMAN.
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU DOWN HERE.
YOU'RE NOT COMIN'?
NOW. WHAT YOU GONNA
SEE AIN'T PRETTY.
BUT IT'S SAFE.
(man)
W.M.D.s. GOT THEM W.M.D.s.
I THINK YOU NEED
TO TAKE THIS JOURNEY
YOUR OWN SELF.
(inaudible)
(man)
GOT THOSE YELLOW.
THOSE YELLOW TOPS.
YELLOW TOPS RIGHT HERE.
(noisy chattering)
(piano music playing)
(people chattering)
I ORDERED ONE FOR YOU.
THANKS.
SURPRISED I CALLED?
A LITTLE.
AFTER THE WAY WE LEFT IT.
HMM.
I'M A TYPE "A." JIMMY.
PEOPLE LIKE ME BREAK THINGS.
WHEN I SLOW DOWN.
OR WHEN I TAKE A MINUTE
TO THINK ABOUT IT. I...
IS THAT YOUR
IDEA OF AN APOLOGY?
I DIDN'T DRIVE
AN HOUR UP 95 TO APOLOGIZE.
I MISSED YOU.
(exhaling deeply)
I MISSED YOU. TOO.
I GUESS.
STILL. SEEMS A LONG WAY
TO COME JUST TO TELL ME THAT.
THEN TURN AROUND
AND DRIVE BACK DOWN TO D.C.
I'M NOT DRIVING BACK TONIGHT.
SO WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
ARE YOU WORKIN' ON A CASE?
MMM-HMM.
IT'S A GOOD ONE.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
ANYTHING INTERESTING?
I DID HEAR
A CRAZY BALTIMORE STORY.
YOU KNOW.
THROUGH THE RUMOR MILL
OF WASHINGTON.
REALLY?
SOME...
RENEGADE POLICE COMMANDER
TAKES IT ON HIMSELF TO. UH...
I DON'T KNOW.
LEGALIZE DRUGS
IN THE PRECINCT?
MAYOR DOESN'T
EVEN KNOW ABOUT IT?
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
CRAZY STORY.
SOMEONE...
I THINK IT'S COLVIN.
YOU KNOW HIM?
NO. I CAN'T SAY THAT I DO.
STILL. I THINK
IT'S FUNNY THAT SOME. UH.
WATER-COOLER TALKER
DOWN IN D.C.
KNOWS ANY
BALTIMORE COP'S NAME.
I WAS JUST WONDERING.
(diners laughing and chattering)
LISTEN. I'M. UH...
YOU'RE LEAVING?
YEAH. I THINK SO.
GOOD NIGHT.
DAMN. MAN.
I MISS THIS CRIB ALREADY.
YEAH. WELL. YOU SPENDIN'
A LOT OF TIME
AT THE OTHER SPOT
DOIN' WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
YEAH.
MAN. IT'S A SHAME
WE GOT TO DEAL
WITH THIS
MARLO BULLSHIT. MAN.
I MEAN. IF I HAD
TAKEN CARE OF THAT
EARLIER. MAN...
THERE'S ALWAYS
GONNA BE A MARLO. MAN.
NO MARLO. NO GAME.
BUT YOU COULD'VE DEALT
WITH THAT SHIT A LITTLE
SOONER. I MEAN. YEAH.
BUT. YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M SAYIN'? DON'T LET IT
LAY ON YOU LIKE THAT.
TONIGHT. I MEAN.
I'M GONNA KICK BACK
AND JUST ENJOY THIS VIEW.
I MEAN.
LOOK AT THIS SHIT.
CAN YOU FUCKIN'
BELIEVE THIS?
I MEAN. I GOT A CRIB
THAT'S OVERLOOKIN'
THE HARBOR.
THIS IS THE SAME PLACE...
WE USED TO RUN
THROUGH THIS MOTHERFUCKER.
WE HAD EVERY
SECURITY GUARD IN THERE
FOLLOWIN' US.
AS THEY SHOULD HAVE.
TRUE. TRUE.
AND THEN THERE
WAS THAT ONE TIME...
TOY STORE?
HELL. YEAH. I TOLD
YOUR ASS NOT TO STEAL
THE BADMINTON SET.
WHAT YOU GONNA DO
WITH A FUCKIN' NET
AND A RACKET AND WE
AIN'T GOT NO YARD.
FUCK.
YOU LIKE. "YO.
THAT WHITE BOY AIN'T GONNA
JUMP OVER THAT COUNTER
AND COME CHASE AFTER ME."
HE SURE DID. THOUGH.
THEN HE SAID...
(whooshing)
I SAID. "WHAT THE FUCK?"
HE WAS ON YOUR
ASS LIKE CARL LEWIS.
FISTS WAS ROLLED UP.
YOUR ASS WAS RUNNIN'. TOO.
FAST AS YOU COULD.
PUNCHIN' YOURSELF
IN THE CHEST.
LOOKIN' ALL MAD AND SHIT.
(screaming)
THAT SHIT
WAS CRAZY. MAN.
RIGHT HERE. TOO. MAN.
RIGHT THERE. GODDAMN.
(distant sirens wailing)
CAN YOU IMAGINE. MAN.
IF I HAD THE MONEY
THAT I HAVE NOW. MAN.
I COULD HAVE
BOUGHT HALF THIS
WATERFRONT PROPERTY.
GOD DAMN IT.
AH. FORGET ABOUT THAT
FOR A WHILE. MAN.
YOU KNOW.
JUST DREAM WITH ME.
WE AIN'T GOTTA
DREAM NO MORE. MAN.
WE GOT REAL SHIT.
REAL ESTATE. WE CAN TOUCH.
I CAN'T GET TOO
FUCKED UP TONIGHT. MAN.
I GOT SOME SHIT
I GOTTA DO ON THE SITE
TOMORROW.
PLUS. THE FUCKIN' POLACK
WE GOT WORKIN' FOR US. MAN.
I GOTTA PULL HIS COAT.
IF HE HAD ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THAT
CLAY DAVIS BULLSHIT. MAN.
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO CUT HIS MONEY.
LITTLE FAGGOT.
WHAT TIME Y'ALL MEETIN'?
UH...
WHAT TIME? UH. 12:00.
UH. I THINK. WHY?
YOU... YOU NEED ME TO DO
SOMETHIN' FOR YOU?
NO. I'M JUST SEEIN'
WHERE YOU GOIN' TO BE AT.
YOU NEED TO RELAX MORE. MAN.
WELL. WHEN THE TIME
IS RIGHT. I WILL.
YOU KNOW. I DON'T TAKE
MY WORK TOO SERIOUSLY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S JUST BUSINESS.
(sighing)
US. MOTHERFUCKER.
US. MAN.
(both grunting)
(boy #1)
GET HIM. ANDRE. GO GET HIM.
(boy #2)
COME ON. SPIDER.
YOU GOT HIM. COME ON.
(bell clanging)
EASY. EASY. EASY.
ALL RIGHT?
I'M GOOD. I'M GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. DITTY. YOU UP.
(boy #1)
WHY DIDN'T YOU
HIT HIM BACK. MAN?
YOU. JUSTIN.
COME ON. BOY.
I'M CALLIN' YOUR NAME.
ALL RIGHT. LISTEN UP.
WE GONNA HAVE 3
2-MINUTE ROUNDS.
WATCH THE LOW BLOWS.
TOUCH GLOVES.
AND...
(clanging)
(boy #2)
LET'S GO. JUSTIN.
JUSTIN. COME ON.
COME ON.
THAT'S GOOD.
(boy #2)
STRAIGHT SHOT.
COME ON.
GET YOUR HANDS UP.
JUSTIN.
COME ON. MAN.
COME ON.
YOU GOTTA BLOCK THAT.
(Cutty)
HE LEADIN' LEFT AND
PUNCHIN' RIGHT. JUSTIN.
MOVE TOWARDS HIS WEAK SIDE.
(boy)
HE ONLY COME UP
TO YOUR WAIST.
(Cutty)
OH. MAN. BELL.
(bell clanging)
THAT WAS
A QUICK 2 MINUTES.
YEAH. I KNOW.
GET YOU SOME WATER.
BOY. AND SPIT IT OUT.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
DIZZY.
THAT'S WHY THE HELL
I KEEP TELLIN' YOU
YOU GOT TO BREATHE. BOY.
SO. WHAT?
YOU HAD ENOUGH?
NO. I'M GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
(bell clanging)
(boy #1)
LET'S GO. JUSTIN.
(boy #2)
LET'S GO. JUSTIN!
COME ON. JUSTIN.
LET'S GO. JUSTIN.
COME ON.
(fighters grunting)
JAB. JUSTIN. GOTTA JAB.
(computer bleeping)
HMM.
HEY. WE'RE UP. HERE IT IS.
(man)
It's me. man.
(Stringer)
You heard from
the fat man?
Yeah.
We low. right?
One mark shy
of the mark.
Yeah. it's light.
Cherry say it's light.
Tell the man I'm doin'
what needs done.
All right. I'll tell him.
Oh. and that other thing?
What?
Them 2 hitters you asked after.
He good with it.
Not on the phone.
(beeping)
THAT'S IT.
WE GOT IT!
(all laughing)
(Pearlman)
GOOD WORK.
(Freamon hooting)
(Freamon)
I GUESS THIS IS PERTINENT.
YEAH!
(boys shouting and cheering)
(bell clanging)
(clapping)
AIN'T NO NEED
TO GO BACK OUT.
YOU AIN'T GOT
TO PROVE NOTHIN'.
SHOOT. MY MOMMA HIT
ME HARDER THAN THAT.
I STILL GOT A CHANCE.
HE GETTIN' TIRED.
MMM-HMM.
DRINK AND SPIT.
READY.
YOU MORE THAN
READY. BOY.
YOU GAME ROOSTER.
(boy #1)
LET'S GO. JUSTIN.
(boy #2)
HEY. JUSTIN.
(boys cheering)
(vehicles passing)
IS THERE
AN ALLEY ENTRANCE?
BOARDED UP
ON BOTH SIDES.
SO WE GONNA HAVE TO
GO THROUGH THE FRONT.
THAT'S A CHANGE
FOR YOU. ISN'T IT?
YOU JUST BE READY.
BOW TIE.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT?
(boys shouting)
BREATHE. BOY. BREATHE.
(Cutty)
TOUCH GLOVES.
HOW'D I DO?
YOU STILL GOT
PLENTY TO LEARN.
BUT ON THE HEART SIDE?
YOU DID GOOD.
(boys cheering)
GO ON HOME. SOLDIER.
YOU DONE FOR THE DAY.
(boy #1)
YEAH. JUSTIN!
(cheering and clapping)
OH. I CAN SEE IT
ALL CLEARLY NOW.
BETWEEN YOU AND
THEM SUBCONTRACTORS
AND THAT
MOTHERFUCKIN' POLITICIAN.
Y'ALL HAD ME
IN A SPIN. RIGHT?
MR. BELL.
I DON'T KNOW...
LITTLE MAN!
WE GONNA GET ALL
THIS SHIT SORTED OUT.
AND. HEY. IF THE SHIT
DON'T COME UP RIGHT.
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER
YOU GONNA PAY FOR THIS SHIT.
LOOK.
I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE ANGRY.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME
YOU CAN SEE THE PROGRESS
WE'VE MADE IN HERE.
PROGRESS.
NOW I HONESTLY
DON'T KNOW WHAT
PASSED BETWEEN YOU
AND SENATOR DAVIS.
BUT IF YOU'RE UNHAPPY
WITH CLAYTON'S PERFORMANCE.
THEN YOU HAVE TO
WORK THAT OUT...
SHIT.
(man)
OH. GOD.
OH. GOD. NO.
(man pleading)
OH. GOD. NO. NO...
(footsteps clattering)
(panting)
I AIN'T STRAPPED.
LOOK. MAN.
I AIN'T INVOLVED.
I AIN'T INVOLVED
IN THAT GANGSTER
BULLSHIT NO MORE.
WHAT Y'ALL NIGGERS
WANT. MAN?
HUH? MONEY?
IS THAT IT?
'CAUSE IF IT IS. MAN.
I CAN BE A BETTER
FRIEND TO Y'ALL ALIVE.
YOU STILL DON'T
GET IT. DO YOU?
HUH?
THIS AIN'T ABOUT
YOUR MONEY. BRO.
YOUR BOY GAVE YOU UP.
(Omar)
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND WE AIN'T HAD TO
TORTURE HIS ASS. NEITHER.
WELL. IT SEEM LIKE...
I CAN'T SAY NOTHIN'
TO CHANGE Y'ALL MINDS.
WELL. GET ON WITH IT.
MOTHER...
(shell casings clinking)
(train rattling by)
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm